RG 005:030, Office of the Governor: James L. McConaughy and James C. Shannon (1947-1949)
Connecticut State Library
James L. McConaughy and James C. Shannon records
1947-1949
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut. Governor (1947-1948: McConaughy)
Connecticut. Governor (1948-1949: Shannon)
21 cubic feet
Gov. James L. McConaughy and Gov. James C. Shannon's correspondence, subject files, and board and commission files.
RG005_030
T001232
Biographical Note
James L. McConaughy
Born: October 21, 1887 at New York, New York.
College: Yale, 1909; Bowdoin M.A., 1911; Columbia Ph.D., 1913; Dartmouth M.A., 1915.
Political Party: Republican.
Offices: Lt. Governor of Connecticut, 1939-1941; Governor of Connecticut, 1947-1948.
Died: March 7, 1948 at Hartford, Connecticut.
James McConaughy was one of several governors of Connecticut in the first half of the twentieth century who came from an academic background. Others were Bingham, Cross and Snow. What they shared with their university activities was a love of politics. McConaughy was born in New York City where his father, a minister, was an official in the Y.M.C.A. His family moved to Massachusetts and in 1901 he attended the Mount Herman School where his father had been on the faculty for ten years. McConaughy received college degrees from four universities and in 1918 was named president of Knox College in Illinois. He became associated with Connecticut when Wesleyan University in Middletown made him its president in 1925. He married Elizabeth Townshend in 1913 and they had three children.
When the new Republican Party of Connecticut emerged after the 1937 death of its long time party boss, J. Henry Roraback, McConaughy became one of its advocates. Known as a forceful speaker, he was one of several candidates being proposed in 1938 for the Republican nomination for governor. When Raymond Baldwin agreed to head the party's ticket that year, he consented to be nominated for the position of lieutenant governor. As with Baldwin, the small Union Party placed him on its ticket and this helped him win the election. McConaughy sought to serve two more years as lieutenant governor, but lost in the 1940 campaign. In 1942 he left Wesleyan to become president of the United Chinese Relief Fund during World War II. A year later he became part of the secret operations of the U.S. government's Office of Strategic Services (OSS). When the 1946 state Republican convention met, McConaughy was nominated for governor and he faced his former Wesleyan associate, Wilbert Snow, in the election. In winning the post, he replaced Snow as governor, who had served the last 13 days of Raymond Baldwin's term.
As governor, McConaughy pushed those programs that interested him, including education, reform in employment, housing needs, benefits for the elderly, and assistance for returning servicemen. To pay for these programs he urged passage of a state sales tax, which brought in more funds than were needed and had to be scaled down later. McConaughy also pushed for the integration of the state's National Guard so that Blacks would not be segregated into separate units. McConaughy suddenly died after serving a little over one year as governor on March 7, 1948. The state's offices, courts and schools closed in his honor. McConaughy was given a small private funeral in Middletown where his remains were cremated. A larger ceremony was held the next day at the Capitol Building in Hartford. McConaughy Hall at the University of Connecticut in Storrs is named in his honor, as is a building at Wesleyan University.
James C. Shannon
Born: July 21, 1896 at Bridgeport, Connecticut.
College: Georgetown, 1918; Yale Law School, 1921.
Political Party: Republican.
Offices: Lt. Governor of Connecticut, 1947-1948; Governor of Connecticut, 1948-1949.
Died: March 6, 1980 at Fairfield, Connecticut.
The second Catholic governor of Connecticut, James Shannon, came from an active political family where both his father and uncle worked in local politics, and his grandfather, Patrick Coughlin, had been a Democratic mayor of Bridgeport in 1888. Shannon attended local schools in Bridgeport and graduated from Georgetown University in 1918. After serving in the U.S. Navy during the First World War, he earned a law degree from Yale in 1921 and returned to Bridgeport to practice law. Shannon served as the city's prosecuting Attorney for 1923-1931 and was a judge on its Juvenile Court for 1931-1935. In 1939 he became the counsel for the Connecticut Federation of Labor, and held that position until he became governor in 1948. Married to Helen M. McMurray in 1925, the Shannons had three children.
Until 1947 Shannon never sought office beyond Bridgeport. He had been approached in 1928 by the state Republican Party to run for Congress, but he refused to do so because of his family. At the 1946 state Republican Convention James McConaughy and Joseph Talbot sought the nomination for governor. In an attempt to avoid a battle among the delegates there, Talbot was urged by the party leadership to accept the nomination of lieutenant governor behind McConaughy. When he refused to do so and McConaughy was certain of victory, the leadership had Governor Raymond Baldwin telephone Shannon at his office in Bridgeport and ask him if he would like to be lieutenant governor. When Shannon replied, "Who wouldn't," he was told to prepare his acceptance speech and to be at the convention in the morning. He was elected to the office in November and when McConaughy died a little more than a year after his inauguration, Shannon became Connecticut's governor and immediately closed the state's agencies, courts and schools in honor of his predecessor. Although he was only in office for ten months, Shannon carried out McConaughy's programs. He did call the General Assembly into special session to face the problem of a lack of housing in the state. He had legislation passed that increased funding for housing and to assist people who faced eviction from their homes.
When the 1948 elections came, Shannon sought to be elected to a full term as governor, but he was defeated in a close campaign by the Democratic candidate, Chester Bowles. Shannon served on Connecticut's Superior Court for 1953-63 and on the state's Supreme Court for 1963-65.
He was active in programs of the Catholic Church, with the Boy Scouts, and with the Bridgeport Y.M.C.A. After his 1980 death he was buried in the Oaklawn Cemetery in Fairfield. His house in Bridgeport still stands and is privately owned.
Bibliography
Congressional Quarterly's Guide to United States Elections. Washington, D.C.: Congressional Quarterly, 1994 [CSL call number GIS Ref JK 1967 .C662 1994.
Glashan, Roy R. American Governors and Gubernatorial Elections, 1775-1975. Stillwater, Minn.: Croixside Press, 1975 [CSL call number JK 2447 .G53 1975].
Hartford Times, March 8, 1948.
Sobel, Robert and John Raimo. Biographical Directory of the Governors of the United States, 1789-1978. Westport, Conn.: Meckler Books, 1978 [CSL call number GIS Ref E 176 .B573].
Van Dusen, Albert E. Connecticut. New York: Random House, 1961 [CSL call number HistRef F 94 .V3].
Scope and Content
Gov. James L. McConaughy and James C. Shannon's records are correspondence and subject files related to state agencies, commissions, legislative bills, and appointments among other topics. Also included are boards and commissions files.
Arrangement
Series 1. Correspondence.
Series 2. Subject Files.
Series 3. Boards and Commissions Files.
Related Material
, Connecticut State Library.
Index Terms
Persons:
McConaughy, James L. (James Lukens), b.1887; Shannon, James C. (James Coughlin), 1896-1980
Subjects:
McConaughy, James L. (James Lukens), b.1887 -- Archives; Shannon, James C. (James Coughlin), 1896-1980 -- Archives; Connecticut. Office of the Governor -- Archives; Connecticut -- History -- Sources; Connecticut -- Politics and government -- 1865-1950 -- Sources; Governors -- Connecticut -- Archives
Document Types:
Correspondence; Records
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Series 1. Correspondence
  - A-C (Box 486)
  - D-H (Box 487)
  - I-N (Box 488)
  - O-S (Box 489)
  - T-Z (Box 490)
- Series 2. Subject Files
  - Adjutant General, 1947 (Box 491)
  - Adjutant General, 1948 (Box 491)
  - Aeronautics Dept. (Box 491)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1947 (Box 491)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1948 (Box 491)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station Conference, Re: One Director For Both or Under Separate Directors (Box 491)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station Re: Minutes of Board of Control [one black binder], 1948 (Box 491)
  - Agriculture Dept. (Box 491)
  - American Overseas Aid United Nations Appeal for Children (Box 491)
  - American School for Deaf (Box 491)
  - Athletic Commissioner, 1947-1948 (Box 492)
  - Attorney General, 1947 (Box 492)
  - Attorney General, 1948 (Box 492)
  - Auditors [half the box] (Box 492)
  - Banking Department, 1947-1948 (Box 493)
  - Blood Donor Service, 1947-1948 (Box 493)
  - Board of Education of the Blind, 1947-1948 (Box 493)
  - Bradley Field, 1947-1948 (Box 493)
  - Cancer Society (Box 493)
  - Census Bureau (Box 493)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1947-1948 (Box 493)
  - C[ongress] I[ndustrial] O[rganizations] (Box 493)
  - Civilian Defense (Box 494)
  - Civil Rights (Box 494)
  - Communist Party, Letters From (Box 494)
  - Community Chest (Box 494)
  - Community Property Law (Box 494)
  - Comptroller, 1948 (Box 494)
  - Comptroller’s - Construction Div[ision] (Box 494)
  - Comptroller’s Office, 1947 (Box 494)
  - Comptroller’s Real Estate Division (Box 494)
  - Conference, Governors’ – Miscellaneous (Box 495)
  - Conference, Governors’ - Hotel Statler, Boston, 1947 November 20-21 (Box 495)
  - Conference on State Defense (Box 495)
  - Congressmen – Correspondence with, 1947 (Box 495)
  - Connecticut Federation of Labor (Box 495)
  - Connecticut Hospital Service (Box 495)
  - Connecticut Labor – Management Advisory Council (Box 495)
  - Connecticut Nautical Cadets (Box 495)
  - Connecticut Prison Assoc[iation] (Box 495)
  - Connecticut Public Expenditure Council (Box 496)
  - Connecticut Reformatory (Box 496)
  - Connecticut Rural Roads Improvement Association (Box 496)
  - Connecticut State Employees Assoc[iation] (Box 496)
  - Connecticut Veterans’ Advisory Com[mission], 1947 (Box 496)
  - Connecticut Veterans’ Advisory Com[mission], 1948 (Box 496)
  - Coroner (Box 496)
  - Council of State Governments (Box 497)
  - Council of State Governments Bulletins (Box 498)
  - County Commissioners (Box 498)
  - County Jail (Box 498)
  - Dairy and Food Commission (Box 498)
  - Development Commission, 1947 (Box 499)
  - Development Commission, 1948 (Box 499)
  - Development Commission Reports (Box 499)
  - Directories (Box 500)
  - Domestic Animals [Commission] (Box 500)
  - Economy Report of Committee of General Assembly (Box 500)
  - Egg Inspection Letters Regarding Inspection of Same (Box 500)
  - Education Department, 1947 (Box 500)
  - Education Department, 1948 (Box 500)
  - Equal Rights Amendment (Box 501)
  - Extraditions (Box 501)
  - F[air] E[mployment] P[ractices] C[ommission] Hearing Examiners Com[mittee] (Box 501)
  - Fairfield County Home (Box 501)
  - Farms and Markets Department (Box 501)
  - Federal Security Agency (Box 501)
  - Finance and Control, 1947 (Box 501)
  - Finance and Control, 1948 (Box 501)
  - [Finance and Control] – Budget Division (Box 501)
  - [Finance and Control] – Purchasing (Box 501)
  - Fish and Game Complimentary Licenses (Box 501)
  - Fish and Game Department (Box 501)
  - Food and Drugs Commission (Box 501)
  - Food Conservation Committee (Box 502)
  - Forest & Wildlife Commission (Box 502)
  - Freight Rate Committee (Box 502)
  - Fuel Advisory Committee, [CT] – Minutes of Meetings (Box 502)
  - Fuel – Correspondence with: Mayors, First Selectmen Re: Fuel Committees Conservation of Fuel (Box 502)
  - Fuel - Correspondence with Newspapers Re: Governor’s Speech on Fuel, Also a copy of Governor's Address, 1948 January 5 (Box 502)
  - Fuel – Correspondence with Oil Companies Re: Fuel Supplies & Reservation of Heating Fuels (Box 502)
  - Fuel – Correspondence with: President, Secretary of Commerce, Navy Dept., Dept. of Interior, Maritime Comm. & Cong[ressional] Delegates (Box 502)
  - Fuel – General File (Box 503)
  - Fuel - Reports from State Department Re: Conservation of Fuel (Box 503)
  - Fuel – Texas Oil Strike Correspondence With: President - Congressional Delegates - American Oil Co[mpany] & Gov. [Robert F.] Bradford [MA] (Box 503)
  - Governor Mc[Conaughy] - Inaugural Address (Box 503)
  - Governor’s Contingent Fund (Box 503)
  - Governors, Correspondence with, 1947 (Box 503)
  - Governors, Correspondence with, 1948 (Box 503)
  - Governors Correspondence with Members of the General Assembly (Box 503)
  - Grain Situation (Box 503)
  - Green Pastures Contest (Box 503)
  - Hawaii Statehood (Box 503)
  - Health Department, 1947 (Box 503)
  - Health Department, 1948 (Box 504)
  - Highway Department, 1947 (Box 504)
  - Highway Department, 1948 (Box 504)
  - Highway Safety Commission, 1947 (Box 505)
  - Highway Safety Commission, 1948 (Box 505)
  - President’s Highway Safety Conf[erence] (Box 505)
  - [Hospitals and Institutions] Fairfield State Hospital (Box 506)
  - [Hospitals and Institutions] Institutions Conference Re: Epidemics (All Institution Heads) (Box 506)
  - [Hospitals and Institutions]] Long Lane School (Box 506)
  - [Hospitals and Institutions] Mansfield - Southbury Training Schools for Conference Re One Director for Both - Or a Director for Each School (Box 506)
  - [Hospitals and Institutions] Mansfield State Training School and Hospital (Box 506)
  - [Hospitals and Institutions] Middletown Hospital (Box 506)
  - [Hospitals and Institutions] Norwich State Hospital (Box 506)
  - [Hospitals and Institutions] Sanatoriums (Box 507)
  - [Hospitals and Institutions] Southbury Training School (Box 507)
  - [Hospitals and Institutions] State Farm for Women (Box 507)
  - [Hospitals and Institutions] State Institution for Deaf (Box 507)
  - Hospital Rates (Box 507)
  - [Housing Authority, Connecticut State “Review of Connecticut’s Housing Problem and Methods to Alleviate the Shortage", 1948 July 1; 2 copies (Box 507)
  - Housing: Correspondence Re: Towns Applying and Towns Refusing State Aid (Box 507)
  - Housing: Funds Allocated for Veterans Housing (Box 507)
  - Housing: General Correspondence, 1947 (Box 508)
  - Housing: General Correspondence, 1948 January-June (Box 508)
  - Housing: General Correspondence, 1948 June-August (Box 508)
  - Housing: General Correspondence, 1948 August-October (Box 508)
  - Housing: General Correspondence, 1948 October-December (Box 508)
  - Housing: Insurance Companies (Box 509)
  - Housing: Joint Committee on Moderate Rental (Gov. – Atty. Gen. - Comptroller - Mr. White) Public Act 405 (Box 509)
  - Housing: Letters from College Students (Box 509)
  - Housing: Letters to Mayor and Senators Re: Allotments to Towns and Cities (Box 509)
  - Housing: Vacancies in Temporary War Housing (Box 509)
  - Housing: Veterans Housing (Box 509)
  - Humane Society (Box 510)
  - Immigration and Naturalization Service (Box 510)
  - Insurance, 1948 (Box 510)
  - Insurance Department (Box 510)
  - Inter-American Commission (Box 510)
  - Inter-Governmental Cooperation Com[mission] (Box 510)
  - Inter - Racial Commission, 1947 (Box 510)
  - Inter - Racial Commission, 1948 (Box 510)
  - Jewish Material Re: Palestine Issue (Box 510)
  - Judge of Probate (Box 511)
  - Judges (Box 511)
  - Judicial Council, Labor Board of Mediation and Arbitration (Box 511)
  - Labor Department, 1947 (Box 511)
  - Labor Department, 1948 (Box 511)
  - Labor Dept. Bulletins (Box 511)
  - Labor - Unemployment Compensation (Box 511)
  - Labor Dept. Tobacco (Box 511)
  - League of Women Voters (Box 511)
  - Legislation – Circular Letter sent to all State Departments and Institutions (Box 512)
  - Legislative Council (Box 512)
  - Legislative Research (Box 512)
  - Legislative Special Session, 1948 (Box 512)
  - Liberia Centennial (Box 512)
  - Library - State (Box 512)
  - Liquor Control Com[mission] (Box 512)
  - Manufacturer’s Association (Box 512)
  - Medical Society (Box 513)
  - Meeks, Everett V. (Box 513)
  - Meriden School for Boys (Box 513)
  - Military Training (Box 513)
  - Milk Administration [one quarter of box] (Box 513)
  - Milk Companies (Box 513)
  - Mock Legislature [Connecticut Intercollegiate] (Box 513)
  - Motor Vehicle (Box 513)
  - National Guard (Box 513)
  - Naval Militia (Box 513)
  - Navy Department (Box 513)
  - Negroes’ Letters Re: Governor’s Stand In Regard To Negroes [Opposed segregation in the National Guard] (Box 514)
  - New England Council (Box 514)
  - New Haven Teachers College (Box 514)
  - Organizations (Box 514)
  - Park & Forest Commission (Box 515)
  - Personnel (Box 515)
  - Plimpton Street Property (Box 515)
  - Police, 1947 (Box 515)
  - Police, 1948 (Box 515)
  - Police Reports (Box 515)
  - Prison [Connecticut State] (Box 516)
  - Proclamations (Box 516)
  - Public Utilities, 1947 (Box 516)
  - Public Utilities, 1948 (Box 516)
  - Public Utilities – Common Carriers Public Welfare, 1948 (Box 516)
  - Public Welfare, 1948 (Box 516)
  - Public Welfare Council, 1947 (Box 516)
  - Public Welfare Council, 1948 (Box 516)
  - Public Welfare Department, 1947 (Box 517)
  - Putnam Phalanx (Box 517)
  - Rent Control (Box 517)
  - Sales Tax, 2 folders (Box 517)
  - Secretary of Defense (Box 517)
  - Secretary of State (Box 518)
  - Secretary of State - Washington, DC (Box 518)
  - Selective Service (Box 518)
  - Senators, Correspondence with, 1947 (Box 518)
  - Senators, Correspondence with, 1948 (Box 518)
  - Sheriffs (Box 518)
  - Silent Guest Fund Campaign (Box 518)
  - Soldiers’ Sailors’ Marines’ Fund (Box 518)
  - State Boundary Line (Box 518)
  - State Chemists (Box 518)
  - State’s Attorney (Box 518)
  - Strikes (Box 518)
  - Summary Process Actions Re: Letters from Clerks, Common Pleas Courts (Box 518)
  - Supreme Court (Box 518)
  - Tax Department, 1947 (Box 518)
  - Tax Department, 1948 (Box 519)
  - Tax Foundation (Box 519)
  - Tax Study Committee (Box 519)
  - Town Grants (Box 519)
  - Treasurer – Veterans Bonus (Box 519)
  - Treasurer’s Office, 1947 (Box 519)
  - Treasurer’s Office, 1948 (Box 519)
  - Treasurer’s Office – Veterans Bond Commission (Box 519)
  - Treasury Department (Box 519)
  - Tuberculosis Commission, 1947 (Box 519)
  - Tuberculosis Commission, 1948 (Box 519)
  - University of Connecticut, 1947 (Box 520)
  - University of Connecticut, 1948 (Box 520)
  - University of Connecticut – Bond Commission (Box 520)
  - University of Connecticut – Minutes of Meetings (Box 521)
  - University of Connecticut – Proposed Medical School (Box 521)
  - University of Connecticut Farm Labor Program (Box 521)
  - Veterans Bonus Appeal Board (Box 521)
  - Veterans Home (Box 521)
  - Veteran’s Service Centers (Box 521)
  - Vetoes, 1947 (Box 521)
  - Water Commission, 1947 (Box 521)
  - Water Commission, 1948 (Box 521)
  - Yale Corporation, [half of the box] (Box 522)
  - Yankee Friend Ship (Box 522)
- Series 3. Boards and Commissions Files
  - Reports [Agencies, Boards and Commissions] (Box 522-523)
    Disarranged.
  - Boards and Commissions Files (Box 524)
  - Accountancy, Board of (Box 524)
  - Accounting and Auditing Functions (Box 524)
  - Alcoholism, Commission on (Box 524)
  - Architectural Board (Box 524)
  - Atlantic States Marine Fisheries Commission (Box 524)
  - Aviation (Box 524)
  - Banking, Advisory Council on (Box 524)
  - Barbers, Board of Examiners of (Box 524)
  - Child Study Home (Box 524)
  - Chiropody Examiners, Board of (Box 524)
  - Chiropractic Examiners, Board of (Box 524)
  - Chronically Ill, Aged & Infirm, Commission on (Box 524)
  - Dams and Reservoirs, Board of Supervision of (Box 524)
  - Dental Commission (Box 524)
  - Displaced Persons (Box 524)
  - Eastern States Exposition, Trustees of the Conn[ecticut] Building at the (Box 524)
  - Embalmers, Board of Examiners of (Box 524)
  - Engineers and Land Surveyors, Board of Registration for Professional (Box 524)
  - Erosion, Committee to Study Shore (Box 524)
  - Fire Prevention and Control, Commission on (Box 525)
  - Flood Control Committee, Governor’s Interstate (Box 525)
  - Flood Control, New England Interstate (Box 525)
  - Fort Griswold and Groton Monument Commission (Box 525)
  - General Statutes, Commission to Revise the (Box 525)
  - Geological & Natural History Survey (Box 525)
  - Groton - New London Bridge Com[mission] (Box 525)
  - Harbor Masters, Recommendations (Box 525)
  - Hartford Bridge Commission (Box 525)
  - Healing Arts, Board of (Box 525)
  - Henry Whitfield House, Trustees of (Box 525)
  - Historical Routes, Committee to Study (Box 525)
  - Homeopathic Medical Exam[ination] B[oar]d (Box 525)
  - Human Resources in Connecticut, Commission to Study (Box 525)
  - Humane and Welfare Institutions Building Program Com[mission] (Box 525)
  - Investment Committee (Box 525)
  - Israel Putnam Memorial Com[mittee] (Box 525)
  - Juvenile Welfare Committee (Box 525)
  - Labor Board to Determine Hours of Labor and Wages of Persons Employed in Construction of State Buildings (Box 525)
  - Labor Board to Determine the Prevailing Rate of Wages in Road and Bridge Work Authority by the State (Box 525)
  - Major General Edwards Memorial, Commission to Select Site and Design for (Box 526)
  - Marketing Authority (Box 526)
  - Mental Hospitals, Committee on Proposed Integration of (Box 526)
  - Merritt Parkway Commission (Box 526)
  - Metropolitan District (Box 526)
  - Milk Regulation Board (Box 526)
  - Mosquito Control Board (Box 526)
  - Natureopathic Examiners, Board of (Box 526)
  - Nursing, Board of Examiners for (Box 526)
  - Old Lyme-Old Saybrook Bridge Com[mission] (Box 526)
  - Opticians, Commission of (Box 526)
  - Optometry, Board of Examiners in (Box 526)
  - Osteopathic Exam[ination] Board (Box 526)
  - Pardons, Board of (Box 526)
  - Personnel Appeal Board (Box 526)
  - Personnel Committee, Advisory (Box 526)
  - Pharmacy Commission (Box 526)
  - Physiotherapy Technicians, Board of (Box 526)
  - Port Survey Commission (Box 526)
  - Poultry Commission (Box 526)
  - Probate Court Commission (Box 526)
  - Psychologists, Board of Examiners of (Box 526)
  - Public Health Council (Box 526)
  - Public School Building Commission (Box 526)
  - Public Utilities Commission (Box 526)
  - Reappointment, Letters to Members of Boards & Commissions Re: (Box 526)
  - Rent Advisory Commission (Box 526)
  - Rent Control Board, Federal (Box 526)
  - Sanitation Commission, Interstate (Box 527)
  - Savings Bank Life Insurance in Conn[ecticut] (Box 527)
  - Savings Banks’ Railroad Investment Committee (Box 527)
  - Scrap Drive Committee (Box 527)
  - Sculpture Commission (Box 527)
  - Shell Fish Commission (Box 527)
  - State Advisory Council (Box 527)
  - State Educational Institutions, Commission for (Box 527)
  - State Employees Retirement Commission (Box 527)
  - State Hospitals and Training Schools for the Mentally Defective, Commission to Study (Box 527)
  - State Institutions, Commission for (Box 527)
  - State Mental Hospitals, Joint Committee of (Box 527)
  - State Real Assets Advisory Committee (Box 527)
  - State Tax Study Commission (Box 527)
  - Steamship Terminals, Commissioners of (Box 527)
  - Tree Examining Board (Box 527)
  - Unemployment Commissioners (Box 527)
  - Unemployment Compensation Act, Advisory Council for the (Box 527)
  - Veterans Home Commission (Box 527)
  - Veterinary Board of Examination & Registration (Box 527)
  - Water Pollution Control Commission, New England Interstate (Box 527)
  - Workmen’s Compensation (Box 527)